<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artigos on Numaer</title>
    <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artigos on Numaer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 11:15:59 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Você sabe o que é o Selo ASA de Qualidade?</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 11:15:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>Compartilhe seus pensamentos. Sinta-se à vontade para adicionar GIFs, vídeos, #hashtags e mais aos seus posts e comentários. Comece comentando abaixo.&#xA;O Selo ASA foi criado à parti das desregulação do curso de Comissário de Voo no Brasil, na certeza de manter uma sintonia de ensino entre as Escolas de Aviação.&#xA;O Selo ASA foi desenvolvido em parceria com as 4 principais empresas áeras contratantes, no ano de 2023.&#xA;A certeza de um ensino profissional de qualiade é o Selo ASA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Como se tornar comissário de voo no Brasil após o fim da obrigatoriedade do curso - RBAC 63</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>A história de formação profissional dos comissáris de voo no Brasil repousa na certeza de construir um perfil profissional em Segurança de Voo e cultura aeronautica.&#xA;Por isso, por mais de 30 anos, a aviação sempre foi regulada pelo Governo Brasileiro. Inicialmente, em 1931, era o DAC - Departamento de Aviação Civil o responsável por cuidar dos cursos de aviação.&#xA;Posteriomente, em 2006, a ANAC - Agência Nacional de Aviação Civil passa a regular o setor aéreo e fiscalizar os curso de comissários de voo, mecânico de aeronaves e pilotos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: Master Jacques Coppenole</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the velvet and silk which surrounded him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter III: Monsieur the Cardinal</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Poor Gringoire! the din of all the great double petards of the Saint-Jean, the discharge of twenty arquebuses on supports, the detonation of that famous serpentine of the Tower of Billy, which, during the siege of Paris, on Sunday, the twenty-sixth of September, 1465, killed seven Burgundians at one blow, the explosion of all the powder stored at the gate of the Temple, would have rent his ears less rudely at that solemn and dramatic moment, than these few words, which fell from the lips of the usher, “His eminence, Monseigneur the Cardinal de Bourbon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter II: Pierre Gringoire</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Nevertheless, as be harangued them, the satisfaction and admiration unanimously excited by his costume were dissipated by his words; and when he reached that untoward conclusion: “As soon as his illustrious eminence, the cardinal, arrives, we will begin,” his voice was drowned in a thunder of hooting.&#xA;“Begin instantly! The mystery! the mystery immediately!” shrieked the people. And above all the voices, that of Johannes de Molendino was audible, piercing the uproar like the fife’s derisive serenade: “Commence instantly!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: The Grand Hall</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.&#xA;The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
